[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What common name is used to refer to the insects from the subfamily Triatominae, mainly found in the Americas?", "correct_answer": "Kissing bugs", "incorrect_answers": ["Lollipop bugs", "Microphone bugs", "Pretty bugs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The famous \u00cele Notre-Dame, an artificial island built from earth excavated for a metropolitan railway, is located in which country?", "correct_answer": "Canada", "incorrect_answers": ["England", "France", "Switzerland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the tornado that occurred on March 18, 1925 and became the deadliest in U.S. history?", "correct_answer": "Tri-State Tornado", "incorrect_answers": ["Oklahoma City Tornado", "Great Natchez Tornado", "1896 St. Louis \u2013 East St. Louis tornado"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the major gap in the ring system around Saturn?", "correct_answer": "Cassini Division", "incorrect_answers": ["Herschel Gap", "The Great Gap", "Galileo Division"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of what country is the kiwi bird a national symbol?  It is also native to that country.", "correct_answer": "New Zealand", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "United Kingdom", "Sumatra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This commercially available non-toxic gas makes up 25% of the Suns mass.  It is used in deep diving to reduce the effects of narcosis.", "correct_answer": "helium", "incorrect_answers": ["nitrogen", "hydrogen", "carbon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Marine 1, launched in 1961, was the first probe to visit another planet.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Blazing Saddles, a meeting was bombed in the town of Rock Ridge. Where was this town meeting held?", "correct_answer": "at the church", "incorrect_answers": ["at the saloon", "at the town hall", "at the ice cream parlour"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is true about all objects that emit heat?", "correct_answer": "They all emit infra-red waves.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are all composed of plasmas.", "They all emit ultraviolet rays.", "They obey Snells Law"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2007 horror movie is based on the self-titled comic book miniseries and is set in Barrow, Alaska.", "correct_answer": "30 Days of Night", "incorrect_answers": ["I Am Legend", "Night Watch", "Twilight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these important events in the history of Opel happened in 1924?", "correct_answer": "Opel installed Germanys first car production line.", "incorrect_answers": ["all of these", "The company was destroyed by a fire.", "Opel opened its first factory outside Germany."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is suggested that you not do several hours before you go into labor?  It could get you embarrassed.", "correct_answer": "Eat food", "incorrect_answers": ["Eat fish", "Have sex", "Talk on the phone"]}]